Ingabire Diane

I am a high school graduate devoted to improving my coding skills, and I have 3+ years of experience working around computers. I long to gain more skills to finish those unfinished projects that were made by me and my group with the thirst of reaching far and climbing our country on a great ladder.

Kamonyi district Southern Province 0798334054 ngabirediane01@gmail.com

SKILLS

- **★** HTML skills
- ★ Problem-solving skills
- ★ Team-working skills
- ★ Coding skills
- ★ Active listening skills
- ★ Communication skills

EXPERIENCE

Inspire, Educate and Empower, Kamonyi - Teacher Assistant

JANUARY 2024 - MAY 2024

I worked in Inspire, Educate, and Empower as an Information and Communication Technologies teacher assistant where I helped students gain more knowledge on how to use a computer.

Saving Group, Kigali City - Manager of a Group Saving account

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

 I am responsible for depositing and withdrawing money in the bank, granting loans, and reminding members that it's time to submit money. I work with a colleague and it is a challenging but fruitful job.

EDUCATION

ECOLE DES SCIENCES BYIMANA, Southern Province - O'level

Certificate

JANUARY 2020 - AUGUST 2023

I have 3+ years of experience in Computer Science and I have a passion for software engineering and creating useful software for different kinds of people.

APAJI MUSHA, Eastern Province - O'level Certificate

JANUARY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2019

I learned general education in this school and I was in charge of different clubs including business where I was a leader.

AWARDS

IEE, (Inspire, Educate, and Empower)

I won a certificate of working in IEE as an ICT Teacher Assistant.

Digital skills Competency Certificate

I obtained a certificate in Digital Skills which included using Excel, Word, Computer Security and so on.

REFERENCES

Teacher of Computer Science for high school

Mugirase Josine 0783794429

<u>Principal of Byimana School of Sciences</u>

Ingabire Jean Marie Vianey 0784690478

Fellow manager in group saving

Iradukunda Kelia 0792957969

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.